(Sheldon:)I'm glad you think so.
(Bernadette:)That's what I
strive to emulate.
(Raj:)Okay, let's see
if this drug works.
(Woman at table:)Can I help you?
(Raj:)Forgive me for staring,
but you're very beautiful.
(Amy:)Thank you.
(Woman:)That's a great accent.
Where are you from?
(Bernadette:)India.
(Raj:)Oh, cool.
I've always wanted to go there.
(Raj:)It's a beautiful country.
You'd love it.
(Raj:)May I join you?
(Woman:)Uh, okay, sure.
Why not?
(Raj:)My name is Dr. Rajesh
Koothrappali,
(Raj:)and this is my friend
Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
(Scene:)Hi.
(Sheldon:)There's no need
to interact with me.
(Sheldon:)I'm just here to observe.
(Woman:)What's he
observing?
(Raj:)We're scientists.
We observe everything.
(Raj:)Here, go buy yourself a scone.